每天都有无数个梦想等待着被实现。
Everyday there are millions of future waiting to be built.
它们始于灵光一闪，
Each one starts with a spark,
或是受启发的一刻。
a moment of inspiration,
随着时间的推移愈发闪亮。
slowly going brighter over time.
(别这样嘛...)
(Come on...)
(Cieo，派对要迟到了)
(Hey Cleo, we're gonna be late for the party.)
(就再等我一分钟！)
(One minute!)
但当我们将想法分享，
But when we share our ideas,
一起工作，
and work together,
面对共同的挑战，
to solve common challenges.
就会有神奇的事情发生。
Something amazing happens.
（这些创造将）启发他人将其应用于新的领域、
Something that sparks others to create new applications,
(超赞！)
(Awesome!)
产生新的想法，
new ideas,
(你的儿子会没事的。)
(Your son is going to be okay.)
和超乎我们想象的新的创造。
new innovations we can only begin to imagine.
解决那些我们无法独自解决的问题，
Solving real problems larger than ourselves.
一起构建未来。
Building the future, together.
你会构建什么样的未来？
GitHub 构建未来(Building the Future) 宣传片
[Outloudvi 译]